Tired of searching for subtitles?
Ray generates them instantly: getray.app
What do you think?
First impressions?
Workmates.
Or friends of friends.
They're standing very close.
It's a crowded bus.
He's smiling.
She's too enthusiastic.
He's being polite
and he keeps looking around.
Maybe he's looking for seats.
Maybe.
Wait. so if I'm talking to a guy
and he's smiling.
it's just out of politeness?
Yeah!
Or he likes you.
It's a pretty wide gulf.
There you go.
That's way too handsy for work colleagues.
God. they're really going for it
with the masks now.
Yeah. it's a little eerie.
It's like the start of a zombie movie.
You know. I got yelled at for standing too
close to somebody at the checkout line.
People are losing their fucking minds.
A guy at work said they're gonna announce
a lockdown soon.
A lockdown?
A lockdown of what?
Of us!
Everyone.
We'll have to stay at home
for. like. two weeks to stop the spread.
We won't be able to leave
except for food and emergencies.
Oh. God. it is like a zombie movie.
Next thing. there's a title card like
'Ten Years Later...'
We've all got beards and shaved heads and
we're fighting over canned meat.
Uh. I'm not fighting you for canned meat;
that's all yours.
And how do you reckon you'd go
with a shaved head?
Knowing my luck.
I'll end up with a beard instead.
See?
Friends of friends.
Aww.
Oh!
What the fuck?
Yeah. there was no need for that.
That's what you do
when we go our separate ways. isn't it?
See you tomorrow.
Unless they lock us down.
Oh. well. if they do. I'll just see you
out in the wastelands then.
I'll be the one with the fucking weird
machete hand or the beard.
Goodbye!
Workers are back in the office
for the first time in
two years after COVID
restrictions have been drawn back.
A lot of the things we haven't been able
to do. we are now able to.
Australians are getting back to work.
Lockdown is over.
but it has come at a huge cost.
Hello. stranger.
Well. well. well.
She returns.
It's been a while.
It's been a long while.
Did you get called back into the office?
Yep.
New management demands it.
And you?
Yep.
Been back for a couple of months now.
So your fucking friend was right?
Who?
Oh. right.
Yeah. he moved to the mountains
right at the start.
Traded the shirt and tie
for a flannel.
Lives off the land now.
Pushed all in on apocalypse. huh?
You got to respect that.
So. what have you been up to for. like.
what. two years?
You know. baking. gardening. ...
No. ahh.
Zoom meetings and existential crisis.
At least you've got both your hands still
and a full head of hair.
No beard. sadly.
Stephen King or Danielle Steele?
Close.
Oh.
Of course.
Is this what you've turned to
in my absence?
Russian philosophy.
What have they done to us?
Well. what kind of ambitious literature
were you reading during lockdown?
Reading?
I just binged Tiger King and Squid Games.
like every other basic arsehole.
So many empty seats.
Yet you sat here.
Well. I'll see you tomorrow. I guess.
Unless...
Hey.
Marry me.
Excuse me?
I promised myself if I ever saw you again.
I'd ask you to marry me.
As much as I really don't want
to go to work today. I don't think
that I can pull the
'I'm late because I'm getting married' card
until at least a couple of weeks in.
Yes. that's smart.
At least until a few weeks in.
Look. I've had a long time
to think about this.
Maybe too much time.
I think Dostoyevsky's had a little too
much influence on you.
Was he running around Russia
proposing to women?
Ouspensky. actually.
Ouspensky.
No. okay. so my grandparents.
back in the day.
they went on eight dates
and they got married
and they've been married for 50 years.
So not only Russian philosophers.
your grandparents are to blame.
They are.
So what. go on eight dates with you
and then...
Well. we don't have to get married
if you don't want. obviously.
Look. I just always liked seeing you
on the bus.
It was easily the highlight of my day.
I didn't think I was going
to see you again.
Me neither.
Who even dates anymore?
I don't know.
It's very old school.
Feels like we've been
doing it wrong lately.
There is a distinct lack of wooing.
We can start small.
Go for coffee?
You're not a fucking weirdo. are you?
I don't think I am.
And I'm not just randomly
asking women to marry me.
Just me.
Yeah. just you.
I don't know. man.
this might fuck up the bus thing
we've got going on.
Yeah. but I think I just did that already.
Hold this.
Is this you?
That's me.
You are a brave one
leaving your Airdrop wide open.
How are you not swimming in dick pics?
I don't think I'm the key demographic.
Are you being serious?
Your last name is Wright?
I mean. I have no reason to lie.
Why?
That's my last name.
Fuck off.
I'm serious.
Ryan Wright.
Oh. God.
We're not related. are we?
Okay. I'm descended
from the English Wrights.
What about you?
Scottish.
My pop did the ancestry genealogy thing
during COVID.
Yeah. same.
Well. fuck. would have made
for a very awkward coffee.
Very.
Well. hey. at least
if we do get married.
I won't have to take your last name
because I already have it.
See. you don't even really need me.
You literally have nothing at all
to lose now.
Well. text me.
Morning. How are you?
Morning. mate.
How are ya?
Morning.
So. guess who came second
in the Over-50s watercolour category
at the art show on the weekend?
Whoever the poor guy was behind you.
I'm betting.
No. it was me.
I was so close.
Oh. my God.
That's amazing.
How did that get second prize?
I'd love to see who won first.
Oh. okay.
That's a bit shit. if you ask me.
You got robbed. Helen.
It's nice to get a little ribbon though.
I'm not going to lie.
Well. don't forget about the rest of us
back here when you're a famous artiste.
Fat chance.
'best dick pics'
Looking at porn again?
So. what if I was. Mike.
there's shit all else to do here.
You know. I could be at home
fucking around and doing nothing.
Lucky you. they want to do
an editorial meeting at five.
Oh. can I just zoom in
from my desk instead?
Nope.
The new overlords require meet presence.
They're psychopaths.
Mike. nobody wants this.
It's better when everyone's
just in their little box on the screen.
Admit it. Em.
you missed everyone here. didn't you?
Smells like beard oil in here.
I hope Gary's retirement is awful.
What a selfish. greedy sellout.
Yeah. I heard he started a charity.
Of course he did.
What a dick.
Meeting time.
Here we go.
Emily.
You look so good in person.
What do I look like on screen?
We can hug again.
Oh. did we ever before?
No. but we should have.
Don't inhale. Nat.
it makes it even weirder.
Okay. okay.
I just really missed you. Both of you.
Oh. Mike too.
That kind of cheapens the sentiment.
Did you both see my email?
Oh. you send quite a few emails. Nat.
do you want to be more specific?
The one about the welcome party for the
new corporate stakeholders.
It's a nice way of putting it.
What about this party?
Oh. it's compulsory.
Sorry.
Ah. welcome everybody.
Well. this is nice. isn't it?
Are we all well?
What time do you finish up?
Okay. where should we begin?
Mike.
Yeah. so did anybody watch Squid Game?
Like. that was amazing.
Excuse me.
you know. like. the last three episodes?
But they were playing that for a while.
You know that? Remember that?
Who's this?
Kidding. About 4.30.
You?
I can leave whenever I want.
4.30 then?
Sure.
Let's get this over with.
Excuse me. do you have any sugar?
Yeah. just in the pot.
Oh.
I got you something for our first date.
A corsage. I hope.
Nnn. nnn.
Jesus.
Who's dick is that?
I don't know.
I just scoured the internet
until I found the best one.
Is this your dream dick?
No.
It's the best one for you.
I was being thoughtful.
So you spent your first day
back at work scrolling
through dicks to find the one
that said the most about me?
That's pretty thoughtful.
Do you feel violated?
A little bit. yeah.
It's kind of like a slap
in the face. isn't it?
Every time.
Every time?
Hmm.
How many times is this happening to you?
I have something of an
online following. so every now
and then I'll just open my
DMs and it's like 'Bang. dicks!'
Everywhere.
Wow.
Cool.
You've never sent one?
No.
Absolutely not.
I mean. I barely look at my own dick.
why would I want to subject
someone else to it?
See. now you're just talking common sense.
Oh. wow. you really do have
a following going on.
You've got the blue tick and everything.
Wait. you're telling me you didn't already
cyberstalk me today?
Honestly. no.
It never really occurred to me.
Why. did you?
Yes.
I didn't even have to put
my detective hat on.
Your socials are wide open.
You really walk between the raindrops.
don't you?
I never really had anything to hide.
I didn't know I was going
to get cyberstalked.
Not even by the girl you want to marry
from the bus?
Yeah.
Can I follow you?
Do you think we're ready for that?
It's a day for living on the edge. I guess.
Tech writer and reviewer!
I thought you said you were a journalist.
Ouch!
No. I didn't mean it.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
I did. Yes.
I was just...
sexing it up.
Ah. OK.
So you get to play with the new iPhones
before they come out. or...
No.
If you put the word smart
in front of anything dumb.
like a smart umbrella or an egg tray.
then I'm spending a few days with it
until I find 500 words.
What does a smart umbrella do?
It tells you when it's about to rain
and where it is if you lose it.
So you write smart reviews about dumb.
smart. dumb products?
I never said they were smart reviews.
Hey. you want to get the table over there?
Yep.
Score.
Let's go.
You said you were an accountant.
Can't really sex that up. can I?
Oh. that's true.
Do you like it?
I don't love it. if I'm honest.
but I don't hate it.
And that used to be enough. maybe.
But not now?
I mean. is anything enough after the last
few years?
What would you rather be doing?
I don't know.
Writing something. probably.
something important.
something not vapid
and hopefully not utter shit.
Well. I look forward to reading that.
I'm sure it's amazing.
What would you rather be doing?
Kind of always wanted
to run a coffee shop like this.
Your dream job is to be a barista?
Yes. and no. kind of.
I just wanted to own it and run it and.
you know. select the beans
and make the menu choices
and all that cool stuff.
Then franchise it and retire to the yacht?
No. just one place
where people can hang out.
That'd be enough for me.
That is actually pretty sweet.
Thank you.
Oh. you ordered for us.
This is like an old school date.
Oh. wait. you're not vegan
or gluten-free or anything?
Maybe I should have stalked you.
This is perfect.
This is exactly what I would have ordered.
And you ordered it without pineapple.
Pineapple can be a dealbreaker.
in my opinion.
It's dicey.
I see what you did there.
Bad!
You don't like pineapple?
I love pineapple. but I would never put it
on a pizza that I was sharing.
It's too divisive.
It's delicious. thank you.
Good.
So circling back. are you meant
to carry this smart umbrella
around with you at all times.
just in case. or...?
You don't carry an umbrella?
Of course not. do you?
Yes.
Now. this isn't the dumb smart one.
this is just the. uh. smart...
normal one.
but it has not failed me yet.
So the huge bag thing
isn't just a fashion trend.
you actually carry
useful things inside them.
Prepare for everything
and you never need any of it.
What do you do if it rains?
I guess I get wet.
So you don't walk through
the raindrops after all?
No.
So...
where do you want to go next time?
Should we play it by ear?
Yeah.
Of course.
Good.
Hey!
Hi!
What are you two up to?
I'm just waiting for him
to decide what to watch.
I don't care what we watch.
It's up to you.
Here's your meds. pop.
Hey!
You're home late.
How was your day?
Yeah. it was okay. yours?
Yeah. yeah. it was good. it was good.
You're being coy.
Now I'm definitely going to grill you.
It's on Ian's Facebook.
We should send it next door.
Don't start another neighborhood war. pop.
I didn't start anything.
Hey. you choose what we watch.
I'm actually going to call it a night.
Are you okay?
Yeah. just had a big day.
You guys enjoy.
Hope you got home safe.
Hey!
How was your first day back?
Everybody pumped to be back in the office.
Everybody except me loved it.
How was your shift?
Yeah. same old.
I did have one guy who came in
who got his hand caught in a metal press.
It just seemed like a
purple glove full of water
just hanging off his wrist.
it was fucking gross.
I don't want to hear this.
You asked.
I was being polite.
Not a lot of feel-good stories
come out of an ER. Emily.
Oh. hey. I have this really annoying
work party next Saturday.
I can't go.
Well. it's compulsory.
For you. maybe.
No. I'm working a double.
Since when?
Fuck. um...
Since I agreed to work a double.
Hey. I was going to cook.
I actually was but I just. um...
well. I couldn't be fucked.
So. are you ready to order some pizzas?
Ah. ...
You know what?
I actually got something on the way home.
so I'm not really hungry.
Yeah. I've heard that bullshit before.
No. I'll get an extra large.
but I'm going to get pineapple.
you can just pick it
off if you want some. right?
Fuck!
You want to come to a party next Saturday?
Sure.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm